Hello, this is the police. What is your
emergency?
I've just seen someone break into a car
outside my flat. They've smashed the
window, and they're going through it now.
Okay, I'm creating a report for a theft
from motor vehicle in progress and will
get police on the way as soon as I have
confirmed some information with you.
What is the exact location of the
vehicle?
It's outside 18 Camden Grove, postcode
SE15, 3XB.
Got it, 18 Camden Grove, SE15, 3XB.
Is the suspect still there.
Yes, he's still there. He's leaning
inside the car now.
Okay, I’m going to take a description of
the suspect from you.
Can you tell me what he's wearing and
what he looks like.
Yes. He's a white male, about 30 years
old, wearing a black jacket and grey
jogging bottoms.
Is anyone else with him.
No, I can’t see anyone with him.
Have you seen any weapons.
It looks like he's used a hammer to smash
the window.
Officers are on the way.
They'll be there within 15 minutes on our
emergency response.
Do you know who owns the vehicle.
No, I don't. It's a silver Toyota Yaris,
but I don't know whose it is.
Can you give me the vehicle registration
number.
Yeah, I can. It's H N, 2 8, Y J, W.
That's H, N, two, eight, Y, J W.
And what's your name.
My name is Jessie Peres.
Spelt, J, E, S, S, I, E.
P, E, R, E, S.
And what is your date of birth.
It's 14th February 1991.
Thanks Jessie.
Can I get your telephone number.
Yes. It's 077, 009, 382, 16. Once again,
077, 009, 382, 16.
And are you calling from the scene or
somewhere else.
I'm calling from my flat, which is at 16
Camden Grove, postcode SE15 3XB.
Okay, got it 16 Camden Grove, SE15, 3XB.
I’m going to give you an incident
reference number, do you have something
to write it down with.
Yes, go ahead.
Your incident reference number is 46195.
Please stay inside, keep yourself safe,
and call us back if anything changes.
Okay, Thank you.